iphoneruler.net 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | iPhoneRuler

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by iPhoneRuler.net and how it is used.  

#### Log Files

Like many other websites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

iPhoneRuler.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/index.asp). iPhoneRuler.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. iPhoneRuler.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on iPhoneRuler.net.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to iPhoneRuler.net and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>
